<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://xuanzhang66.github.io</id>
    <title>Xuan ZHANG@Tsinghua University</title>
    <updated>2019-06-17T08:20:47.647Z</updated>
    <generator>https://github.com/jpmonette/feed</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://xuanzhang66.github.io"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://xuanzhang66.github.io/atom.xml"/>
    <subtitle>Xuan ZHANG</subtitle>
    <logo>https://xuanzhang66.github.io/images/avatar.png</logo>
    <icon>https://xuanzhang66.github.io/favicon.ico</icon>
    <rights>All rights reserved 2019, Xuan ZHANG@Tsinghua University</rights>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[å…³äº]]></title>
        <id>https://xuanzhang66.github.io/post/about</id>
        <link href="https://xuanzhang66.github.io/post/about">
        </link>
        <updated>2019-01-25T11:09:48.000Z</updated>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h3 id="curriculum-vitae-xuan-zhangtsinghua-university">Curriculum Vitae, Xuan ZHANG@Tsinghua University</h3>
<h3 id="table-of-contents">Table of Contents</h3>
<ul>
<li><a href="#education">Education</a></li>
<li><a href="#honors-and-awards">Honors &amp; Awards</a></li>
<li><a href="#academic-research-experience">Academic Research Experience</a></li>
<li><a href="#journal-papers">Journal Papers</a></li>
<li><a href="#conference-papers">Conference Papers</a></li>
<li><a href="#papers-under-review-and-to-submit">Papers under Review &amp; to Submit</a></li>
<li><a href="#patents">Patents</a></li>
<li><a href="#research-interest">Research Interest</a></li>
<li><a href="#concurrent-appointments-and-other-activities">Concurrent Appointments &amp; Other Activities</a></li>
<li><a href="#computer-expertise">Computer Expertise</a></li>
</ul>
<p><img src="http://wx4.sinaimg.cn/small/007B55rcly1g2yl41em2gj30sg0sgkf1.jpg" alt=""></p>
<p><strong>Xuan ZHANG</strong>, Ph.D.<br>
Department of Energy and Power Engineering, Tsinghua University<br>
No. 1, Qinghua Yuan, Haidian District, Beijing 100084, P.R.China<br>
Tel: +86-15201619077<br>
Email: <a href="mailto:xuanzhang66@gmail.com">xuanzhang66@gmail.com</a><br>
Website: <a href="https://www.xuanzhang.online">https://www.xuanzhang.online</a><br>
Google Scholar: <a href="https://scholar.google.com/citations?user=9X0KOmYAAAAJ">https://scholar.google.com/citations?user=9X0KOmYAAAAJ</a></p>
<h3 id="education">Education</h3>
<ul>
<li><em><strong>Sep, 2014 ~ Present</strong></em><br>
<strong>Ph.D.</strong> in Power Engineering and Engineering Thermophysics. (Ranking 5/50)<br>
Tsinghua University (THU), Beijing, China.<br>
Thesis title: Research on Freezing and Impact Processes of Supercooled Water Droplet and Their Coupling Characteristics.<br>
Advisor: Prof. Xiaomin Wu.</li>
<li><em><strong>Sep, 2010 ~ Jul, 2014</strong></em><br>
<strong>B.E.</strong> in Thermal Energy and Power Engineering. (Ranking 1/57)<br>
Beijing Institute of Technology (BIT), Beijing, China.<br>
Dissertation title: Study on Gas Resistance in Two-phase Flow Boiling.<br>
Advisor: Prof. Weizheng Zhang.<br>
<a href="#table-of-contents">Back to Top â†‘</a></li>
</ul>
<h3 id="honors-and-awards">Honors and Awards</h3>
<ol>
<li>National Scholarship for Graduate Student (top 0.2% student all over China), Ministry of Education of P.R.China, 2018.</li>
<li>First Rank Award, 3rd National Undergraduate Engineering Training Integration Ability Competition, Ministry of Education of P.R.China, 2013.</li>
<li>Second Rank Award, 13rd &quot;Challenge Cup&quot; National Undergraduate Curricular Academic Science and Technology Works Competition, Ministry of Education of P.R.China &amp; China Association for Science and Technology, 2013.</li>
<li>National Scholarship for Undergraduate Student (top 0.2% student all over China), Ministry of Education of P.R.China, 2012.</li>
<li>National Scholarship for Undergraduate Student (top 0.2% student all over China), Ministry of Education of P.R.China, 2011.</li>
<li>Third Rank Award, 3rd National Undergraduate Mathematical Competition, Chinese Mathematical Society, 2011.</li>
<li>Outstanding Undergraduate Award (top 5% student in Beijing), Beijing Municipal Education Commission, 2014.</li>
<li>First Rank Award, 2nd Capital Undergraduate Engineering Training Integration Ability Competition, Beijing Municipal Education Commission, 2013.</li>
<li>First Rank Award, 7th &quot;Challenge Cup&quot; Capital Undergraduate Curricular Academic Science and Technology Works Competition, Beijing Municipal Education Commission &amp; Beijing Municipal Science and Technology Commission, 2013.</li>
<li>Second Rank Award, 1st Capital Undergraduate Robot Competition, Beijing Municipal Education Commission, 2012 .</li>
<li>Second Rank Award, 28th National (Part Regions) Undergraduate Physics Competition, Beijing Physical Society, 2011.</li>
<li>First Prize Scholarship for Excellent Student, Tsinghua University, 2017.</li>
<li>First Prize of Guanghua Scholarship for Excellent Student, Tsinghua University, 2016.</li>
<li>Tongfang Scholarship for Student Work, Tsinghua University, 2016~2018.</li>
<li>First Prize of Gaotian Scholarship for Excellent Student, Tsinghua University, 2015.</li>
<li>Xu Teli (First president of BIT) Scholarship (one of 20 students awarded over 26,000 students in BIT), Beijing Institute of Technology, 2013.</li>
<li>Professional Star Award, Beijing Institute of Technology, 2013.</li>
<li>Science and Technology Competition Scholarship, Beijing Institute of Technology, 2013.</li>
<li>Pacemaker to Excellent Student (top 1% student in BIT), Beijing Institute of Technology, 2011~2013.</li>
<li>First Prize Scholarship for Excellent Student (top 5% student in BIT), Beijing Institute of Technology, 2010~2014.<br>
<a href="#table-of-contents">Back to Top â†‘</a></li>
</ol>
<h3 id="academic-research-experience">Academic Research Experience</h3>
<ul>
<li>
<p><em><strong>Jan, 2015 ~ Present</strong></em><br>
<strong>National Key Basic Research Program of China</strong>, Research on Key Basic Problems of Aircraft Icing Safety and Its Protection (No. 2015CB755800), Ministry of Science and Technology of P.R.China.</p>
<ul>
<li>Establishing an experimental system to investigate the droplet nucleation/ freezing/impacting characteristics and to explore the effects of environmental conditions, surface wettability, droplet size, etc.</li>
<li>Developing a theoretical model to predict the freezing behaviors of a supercooled water droplet including the formation of final pointy tip.</li>
<li>Simulating the evolution of freezing front based on theoretical model and Fluent VOF model, proposing a correlation to estimate the freezing time.</li>
<li>Experimentally studying the impacting process and post-impact oscillation of room-temperature and supercooled water droplets on different wettabilities surfaces at different We numbers using high speed camera, proposing a correlation for the maximum spreading factor and it corresponding time.</li>
<li>Exploring the effects of the droplet initial shape on the maximum spreading factor and it corresponding time during droplet impact process using Fluent VOF model with dynamic contact angle (DCA).</li>
<li>Developing an aircraft icing model considering both rime ice property variability and runback water effect, exploring the effects of airflow parameters.</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>
<p><em><strong>Jan, 2015 ~ Present</strong></em><br>
<strong>National Natural Science Foundation Program of China</strong>, Relationship Between the Surface Micro-nano Structure and Behavior of Cross-scale Droplets and It Regulation (No. 51476084).</p>
<ul>
<li>Developing methods to fabricate different wettabilities surfaces, studying the droplet behaviors during condensation.</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>
<p><em><strong>Jun, 2016 ~ Aug, 2016</strong></em><br>
<strong>Enterprise Practice Project</strong>, Study on the Bubble Motion in the Edge-Channel of Rotor Compressor Motor, Guangdong Meizhi Compressor Co., Ltd.</p>
<ul>
<li>Establishing a simulation model to predict the bubble motion in the edge-channel of rotor compressor motor as well as the oil return rate, providing the optimized size of the edge-channel.</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>
<p><em><strong>Sep, 2014 ~ Jun, 2015</strong></em><br>
<strong>School Enterprise Cooperation Project</strong>, Simulation Study on Frosting on the Fi Surfaces, Daikin Industries, Ltd.</p>
<ul>
<li>Simulating the frosting process on cold surface using Fluent Eulerian model and UDF file, investigating the effects of airflow parameters and surface conditions.</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>
<p><em><strong>Oct, 2013 ~ Jul, 2014</strong></em>
<strong>Undergraduate Thesis</strong>, Study on Gas Resistance in Two-Phase Flow Boiling, Beijing Institute of Technology.</p>
<ul>
<li>Setting up an experimental system to investigate the flow boiling characteristics including the pressure drop, pressure fluctuation and bubble behaviors.</li>
<li>Simulating the pressure drop using Fluent Mixture model, developing a theoretical model to predict the bubble disappearance.</li>
<li>Analyzing the time-frequency characteristics of pressure fluctuation in flow boiling using signal processing methods (FFT, PSD, etc.).</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>
<p><em><strong>Sep, 2011 ~ Jul, 2013</strong></em><br>
<strong>Undergraduate Innovation Training Program</strong>, Beijing Institute of Technology.<br>
<a href="#table-of-contents">Back to Top â†‘</a></p>
</li>
</ul>
<h3 id="journal-papers">Journal Papers</h3>
<ol>
<li><em><strong>X. Zhang</strong></em>, X. Liu, J.C. Min, X.M. Wu. Shape variation and unique tip formation of a sessile water droplet during freezing. Appl. Therm. Eng. 147, 927-934 (2019), DOI: <a href="https://dx.doi.org/10.1016/j.applthermaleng.2018.09.040">10.1016/j.applthermaleng.2018.09.040</a>.</li>
<li><em><strong>X. Zhang</strong></em>, X. Liu, X.M. Wu, J.C. Min. Experimental investigation and statistical analysis of icing nucleation characteristics of sessile water droplets. Exp. Therm. Fluid Sci. 99, 26-34 (2018), DOI: <a href="https://dx.doi.org/10.1016/j.expthermflusci.2018.07.027">10.1016/j.expthermflusci.2018.07.027</a>.</li>
<li><em><strong>X. Zhang</strong></em>, X. Liu, X.M. Wu, J.C. Min. Simulation and experiment on supercooled sessile water droplet freezing with special attention to supercooling and volume expansion effects. Int. J. Heat Mass Transfer 127, 975-985 (2018), DOI: <a href="https://dx.doi.org/10.1016/j.ijheatmasstransfer.2018.07.021">10.1016/j.ijheatmasstransfer.2018.07.021</a>.</li>
<li><em><strong>X. Zhang</strong></em>, X.M. Wu. Time and frequency characteristics of pressure fluctuations during subcooled nucleate flow boiling. Heat Transfer Eng. 39, 642-653 (2018), DOI: <a href="https://dx.doi.org/10.1080/01457632.2017.1325670">10.1080/01457632.2017.1325670</a>.</li>
<li><em><strong>X. Zhang</strong></em>, X.M. Wu, J.C. Min, X. Liu. Modelling of sessile water droplet shape evolution during freezing with consideration of supercooling effect. Appl. Therm. Eng. 125, 644-651 (2017), DOI: <a href="https://dx.doi.org/10.1016/j.applthermaleng.2017.07.017">10.1016/j.applthermaleng.2017.07.017</a>.</li>
<li><em><strong>X. Zhang</strong></em>, X.M. Wu, J.C. Min. Freezing and melting of a sessile water droplet on a horizontal cold plate. Exp. Therm. Fluid Sci. 88, 1-7 (2017), DOI: <a href="https://dx.doi.org/10.1016/j.expthermflusci.2017.05.009">10.1016/j.expthermflusci.2017.05.009</a>.</li>
<li><em><strong>X. Zhang</strong></em>, X.M. Wu, J.C. Min. Aircraft icing model considering both rime ice property variability and runback water effect. Int. J. Heat Mass Transfer 104, 510-516 (2017), DOI: <a href="https://dx.doi.org/10.1016/j.ijheatmasstransfer.2016.08.086">10.1016/j.ijheatmasstransfer.2016.08.086</a>.</li>
<li><em><strong>X. Zhang</strong></em>, J.C. Min, X.M. Wu. Model for aircraft icing with consideration of property-variable rime ice. Int. J. Heat Mass Transfer 97, 185-190 (2016), DOI: <a href="https://dx.doi.org/10.1016/j.ijheatmasstransfer.2016.01.065">10.1016/j.ijheatmasstransfer.2016.01.065</a>.</li>
<li>F.Q. Chu, Z.P. Yuan, <em><strong>X. Zhang</strong></em>, X.M. Wu. Energy analysis of droplet jumping induced by multi-droplet coalescence: The influences of droplet number and droplet location. Int. J. Heat Mass Transfer 121, 315-320 (2018), DOI: <a href="https://dx.doi.org/10.1016/j.ijheatmasstransfer.2018.01.027">10.1016/j.ijheatmasstransfer.2018.01.027</a>.</li>
<li>Y.C. Tang, J.C. Min, <em><strong>X. Zhang</strong></em>, G.L. Liu. Meniscus behaviors and capillary pressures in capillary channels having various cross-sectional geometries. Chinese J. Chem. Eng. 26, 2014-2022 (2018), DOI: <a href="https://dx.doi.org/10.1016/j.cjche.2018.04.031">10.1016/j.cjche.2018.04.031</a>.</li>
<li>F.Q. Chu, X.M. Wu, B. Zhu, <em><strong>X. Zhang</strong></em>. Self-propelled droplet behavior during condensation on superhydrophobic surfaces. Appl. Phys. Lett. 108, 194103 (2016), DOI: <a href="https://dx.doi.org/10.1063/1.4949010">10.1063/1.4949010</a>.</li>
<li><em><strong>X. Zhang</strong></em>, X.M. Wu, J.C. Min. Numerical simulation of freezing process of a sessile supercooled water droplet on a cold wall. Journal of Engineering Thermophysics 39(01), 159-164 (2018). (In Chinese)</li>
<li>X. Liu, <em><strong>X. Zhang</strong></em>, J.C. Min. Shape variation of sessile water droplet during freezing. Journal of Engineering Thermophysics, 40(1) 2019. (In Chinese)</li>
<li>F.Q. Chu, X.M. Wu, <em><strong>X. Zhang</strong></em>, Y. Zhu. Droplet behaviors and growth regimes on superhydrophobic surfaces. Journal of Engineering Thermophysics 37(07), 1527-1531 (2016). (In Chinese)<br>
<a href="#table-of-contents">Back to Top â†‘</a></li>
</ol>
<h3 id="conference-papers">Conference Papers</h3>
<ol>
<li><em><strong>X. Zhang</strong></em>, X.M. Wu, J.C. Min, X. Liu. Impact of a supercooled water droplet on different temperature and contact angle cold plates, Proceedings of 16th International Heat Transfer Conference, Beijing, China, August 2018, IHTC16-23531.</li>
<li><em><strong>X. Zhang</strong></em>, X.M. Wu, J.C. Min, X. Liu. Shape variation of a sessile droplet during freezing. Proceedings of 6th Asian Symposium on Computational Heat Transfer and Fluid Flow, Chennai, India, December 2017, ASCHT 2017-107.</li>
<li><em><strong>X. Zhang</strong></em>, J.C. Min, X.M. Wu. Effects of airflow parameters on aircraft icing characteristics. Proceedings of 1st Asian Conference on Thermal Sciences, Jeju, Korea, March 2017, ACTS-P00285.</li>
<li><em><strong>X. Zhang</strong></em>, X. Liu, X.M. Wu, J.C. Min, Numerical simulations of freezing process of a sessile supercooled water droplet using Eulerian method. Proceedings of 9th International Symposium on Heat Transfer, Beijing, China, August 2016, ISHT9-K0370.</li>
<li>X. Liu, <em><strong>X. Zhang</strong></em>, J.C. Min. Simulation of droplet impact on a spherical surface. APS March Meeting 2019 , Boston, US, March 2019, G70.00399.</li>
<li>X. Liu, <em><strong>X. Zhang</strong></em>, J.C. Min, X.M. Wu, Experiment on droplet impacting on a spherical surface. Proceedings of 15th International Conference on Flow Dynamics, Sendai, Japan, Novermber 2018, OS18-89.</li>
<li>X. Liu, <em><strong>X. Zhang</strong></em>, J.C. Min, X.M. Wu, Spreading and oscillation on different wettability surfaces at low weber number. Proceedings of 15th International Conference on Flow Dynamics, Sendai, Japan, Novermber 2018, OS18-88.</li>
<li>F.Q. Chu, X.M. Wu, <em><strong>X. Zhang</strong></em>, A theoretical model for the self-propelled droplet jumping phenomenon. Proceedings of 9th International Symposium on Heat Transfer, Beijing, China, August 2016, ISHT9-A0244.<br>
<a href="#table-of-contents">Back to Top â†‘</a></li>
</ol>
<h3 id="papers-under-review-and-to-submit">Papers under Review and to Submit</h3>
<ol>
<li>X. Liu, <em><strong>X. Zhang</strong></em>, J.C. Min. Spreading of droplet impacting on various wettability surfaces at a Weber number close to zero. Experimental Thermal and Fluid Science. (Under Review)</li>
<li>F.Q. Chu, S.K. Li, <em><strong>X. Zhang</strong></em>, H.C. Jin, J. Zhang, X.M. Wu, D.S. Wen, Bubble formation in freezing droplets during icing and condensation frosting, Physical Review Letters. (Under Review)</li>
<li><em><strong>X. Zhang</strong></em>, X. Liu, X.M. Wu, J.C. Min. Droplet impacting and post-impact oscillation processes on different wettability surfaces. Applied Surface Science. (To Submit)</li>
<li><em><strong>X. Zhang</strong></em>, X. Liu, J.C. Min, X.M. Wu. Effect of droplet initial shape on the maximum spreading during impacting process, Journal of Colloid and Interface Science. (To Submit)</li>
<li><em><strong>X. Zhang</strong></em>, X. Liu, J.C. Min, X.M. Wu. Adhesion and rebound of supercooled droplets impacting on a horizontal cold surface, International Journal of Heat and Mass Transfer. (To Submit)<br>
<a href="#table-of-contents">Back to Top â†‘</a></li>
</ol>
<h3 id="patents">Patents</h3>
<ol>
<li><em><strong>X. Zhang</strong></em>, S.Q. Ma, S. Jin, D.X. Xie, T. Fu, K. Zhou, X.Y. Wang. A spatial crank and rocker mechanism capable of precisely adjusting swing angle and direction, Chinese National Utility Model Patent, ZL 201320729918.0. Issued October 2014.<br>
<a href="#table-of-contents">Back to Top â†‘</a></li>
</ol>
<h3 id="research-interest">Research Interest</h3>
<ul>
<li>Droplet freezing and condensation, Supercooled water, .</li>
<li>Droplet dynamics, Wettability, Surface and interface science.</li>
<li>Icing/Frosting formation and prevention.</li>
<li>Micro-/Nano-scale heat and mass transfer, Microfluid.</li>
<li>Phase change energy storage, Phase change materials (PCM).<br>
<a href="#table-of-contents">Back to Top â†‘</a></li>
</ul>
<h3 id="concurrent-appointments-and-other-activities">Concurrent Appointments and Other Activities</h3>
<ul>
<li>
<p><em><strong>Nov, 2018</strong></em><br>
<strong>Referee of Journal of Enhanced Heat Transfer</strong> (Begell House).<br>
Responsibilities: I was invited to review a manuscript and provide my suggestions on publication decision to editor.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p><em><strong>Mar, 2015 ~ Present</strong></em>
<strong>Teaching Assistant</strong>, Engineering Thermodynamics MOOC (Selected as National Excellent Online Open Course of Ministry of Education), Tsinghua University.<br>
Responsibilities: preparing and organizing all the videos and documents needed for the course establishment, answering questions for students online, organizing and maintaining and the course website.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p><em><strong>Sep, 2016 ~ Present</strong></em><br>
<strong>Secretary of Defense on Dissertation for Master's Degree</strong>, Tsinghua University.<br>
Responsibilities: answering the questions from the degree applicants, preparing and organizing the documents needed for the defense, recording the communication between committee and applicant in the defense, keeping the defense order.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p><em><strong>Sep, 2012 ~ Jul, 2014</strong></em><br>
<strong>Class Vice President</strong>, Beijing Institute of Technology.<br>
Responsibilities: managing the affairs in the class, organizing the daily activities for classmates, improving the communications between teachers and classmates.<br>
<a href="#table-of-contents">Back to Top â†‘</a></p>
</li>
</ul>
<h3 id="computer-expertise">Computer Expertise</h3>
<ul>
<li>CAE softwares: AutoCAD, ProE, Solidworks, SketchUp.</li>
<li>CFD softwares: Gambit, ICME CFD, Fluent, Tecplot, OpenFOAM, CFX, COMSOL.</li>
<li>Programming tools: Matlab, C/C++, Python, Fortran, Maple, Mathematics.</li>
<li>Others: LabVIEW, MS Office, Origin, Visio, Endnote.<br>
<a href="#table-of-contents">Back to Top â†‘</a></li>
</ul>
<p><em><strong>Thanks for your visiting!</strong></em></p>
]]></content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hello Gridea]]></title>
        <id>https://xuanzhang66.github.io/post/hello-gridea</id>
        <link href="https://xuanzhang66.github.io/post/hello-gridea">
        </link>
        <updated>2018-12-11T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>ğŸ‘  æ¬¢è¿ä½¿ç”¨ <strong>Gridea</strong> ï¼<br>
âœï¸  <strong>Gridea</strong> ä¸€ä¸ªé™æ€åšå®¢å†™ä½œå®¢æˆ·ç«¯ã€‚ä½ å¯ä»¥ç”¨å®ƒæ¥è®°å½•ä½ çš„ç”Ÿæ´»ã€å¿ƒæƒ…ã€çŸ¥è¯†ã€ç¬”è®°ã€åˆ›æ„... ...</p>
]]></summary>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>ğŸ‘  æ¬¢è¿ä½¿ç”¨ <strong>Gridea</strong> ï¼<br>
âœï¸  <strong>Gridea</strong> ä¸€ä¸ªé™æ€åšå®¢å†™ä½œå®¢æˆ·ç«¯ã€‚ä½ å¯ä»¥ç”¨å®ƒæ¥è®°å½•ä½ çš„ç”Ÿæ´»ã€å¿ƒæƒ…ã€çŸ¥è¯†ã€ç¬”è®°ã€åˆ›æ„... ...</p>
<!-- more -->
<p><a href="https://github.com/getgridea/gridea">Github</a><br>
<a href="http://hvenotes.fehey.com/">Gridea ä¸»é¡µ</a><br>
<a href="http://fehey.com/">ç¤ºä¾‹ç½‘ç«™</a></p>
<h2 id="ç‰¹æ€§">ç‰¹æ€§ğŸ‘‡</h2>
<p>ğŸ“  ä½ å¯ä»¥ä½¿ç”¨æœ€é…·çš„ <strong>Markdown</strong> è¯­æ³•ï¼Œè¿›è¡Œå¿«é€Ÿåˆ›ä½œ</p>
<p>ğŸŒ‰  ä½ å¯ä»¥ç»™æ–‡ç« é…ä¸Šç²¾ç¾çš„å°é¢å›¾å’Œåœ¨æ–‡ç« ä»»æ„ä½ç½®æ’å…¥å›¾ç‰‡</p>
<p>ğŸ·ï¸  ä½ å¯ä»¥å¯¹æ–‡ç« è¿›è¡Œæ ‡ç­¾åˆ†ç»„</p>
<p>ğŸ“‹  ä½ å¯ä»¥è‡ªå®šä¹‰èœå•ï¼Œç”šè‡³å¯ä»¥åˆ›å»ºå¤–éƒ¨é“¾æ¥èœå•</p>
<p>ğŸ’»  ä½ å¯ä»¥åœ¨ <strong>ğ–¶ğ—‚ğ—‡ğ–½ğ—ˆğ—ğ—Œ</strong> æˆ– <strong>ğ–¬ğ–ºğ–¼ğ–®ğ–²</strong> è®¾å¤‡ä¸Šä½¿ç”¨æ­¤å®¢æˆ·ç«¯</p>
<p>ğŸŒ  ä½ å¯ä»¥ä½¿ç”¨ <strong>ğ–¦ğ—‚ğ—ğ—ğ—ğ–» ğ–¯ğ–ºğ—€ğ–¾ğ—Œ</strong> æˆ– <strong>Coding Pages</strong> å‘ä¸–ç•Œå±•ç¤ºï¼Œæœªæ¥å°†æ”¯æŒæ›´å¤šå¹³å°</p>
<p>ğŸ’¬  ä½ å¯ä»¥è¿›è¡Œç®€å•çš„é…ç½®ï¼Œæ¥å…¥ <a href="https://github.com/gitalk/gitalk">Gitalk</a> æˆ– <a href="https://github.com/SukkaW/DisqusJS">DisqusJS</a> è¯„è®ºç³»ç»Ÿ</p>
<p>ğŸ‡¬ğŸ‡§  ä½ å¯ä»¥ä½¿ç”¨<strong>ä¸­æ–‡ç®€ä½“</strong>æˆ–<strong>è‹±è¯­</strong></p>
<p>ğŸŒ  ä½ å¯ä»¥ä»»æ„ä½¿ç”¨åº”ç”¨å†…é»˜è®¤ä¸»é¢˜æˆ–ä»»æ„ç¬¬ä¸‰æ–¹ä¸»é¢˜ï¼Œå¼ºå¤§çš„ä¸»é¢˜è‡ªå®šä¹‰èƒ½åŠ›</p>
<p>ğŸ–¥  ä½ å¯ä»¥è‡ªå®šä¹‰æºæ–‡ä»¶å¤¹ï¼Œåˆ©ç”¨ OneDriveã€ç™¾åº¦ç½‘ç›˜ã€iCloudã€Dropbox ç­‰è¿›è¡Œå¤šè®¾å¤‡åŒæ­¥</p>
<p>ğŸŒ± å½“ç„¶ <strong>Gridea</strong> è¿˜å¾ˆå¹´è½»ï¼Œæœ‰å¾ˆå¤šä¸è¶³ï¼Œä½†è¯·ç›¸ä¿¡ï¼Œå®ƒä¼šä¸åœå‘å‰ğŸƒ</p>
<p>æœªæ¥ï¼Œå®ƒä¸€å®šä¼šæˆä¸ºä½ ç¦»ä¸å¼€çš„ä¼™ä¼´</p>
<p>å°½æƒ…å‘æŒ¥ä½ çš„æ‰åå§ï¼</p>
<p>ğŸ˜˜ Enjoy~</p>
]]></content>
    </entry>
</feed>